Christmas with a View is a tv movie, romance,
family film directed by Justin G. Dyck.
This Christmas, Thunder Mountain Ski Resort is abuzz when
celebrity chef Shane Roarke is named the new head chef.
Clara Garrison isn't as excited and is instead focused on getting resettled
after her failed attempt at opening a restaurant in the city.
With their paths constantly crossing, will their shared passion for
cooking bring them together or will secrets keep them apart?
Clara Garrison, played by Kaitlyn Leeb.
Shane, played by Scott Cavalheiro.
Clive, played by Joseph Cannata.
Lydia, played by Vivica A. Fox.
Frank Haven, played by Patrick Duffy.
Maude, played by Nicole Stamp.
The Christmas Chronicles is a 2018 American Christmas comedy film
directed by Clay Kaytis from a screenplay by Matt Lieberman.
The film stars Kurt Russell, Judah Lewis, Darby Camp, Lamorne
Morris, Kimberly Williams-Paisley, and Oliver Hudson.
It is the first installment in The Christmas Chronicles film series.
The film was produced by 1492 Pictures and Wonder Worldwide and
was released on November 22, 2018, on Netflix.
The plot follows two children, Kate and Teddy, who notice Santa Claus in their home and jump into his sleigh with
his reindeer; however, they accidentally cause the sleigh to crash, and the presents are lost.
As Christmas morning approaches, it is up to the children and Santa to
save Christmas by correctly delivering all of the presents.
The Christmas Chronicles received mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel, titled The Christmas Chronicles 2, was released on November
25, 2020, with much of the original cast returning.
The film explores themes of celebrity, ski resort, christmas.
The tone is emotional.